{
  "title": "Master Questionnaire",
  "slug": "master-questionnaire",
  "description": "",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "23489ae8-fb04-4474-849c-50500b7fab56",
      "text": "the date and time of encounter been recorded",
      "type": "dateTime",
      "link_id": "Q-1750334193911",
      "required": true
    },
    {
      "id": "a66a38a5-c62b-49aa-a1a4-44098396aeee",
      "text": "Does the patient shows have any medication information",
      "type": "boolean",
      "link_id": "Q-1750328670426"
    },
    {
      "id": "adc6efb2-0c64-47fb-b3bc-44c947036b9f",
      "text": "Medication Diagnosis",
      "type": "group",
      "link_id": "Q-1750328887909",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": "3afbbc89-fcb9-417d-b177-b012a88fe1ce",
          "text": "Medication Prescribed (Request)",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750329455223",
          "structured_type": "medication_request"
        },
        {
          "id": "59fce5bd-b5a4-42e9-b8c7-6e12758534a4",
          "text": "Medication Statement (History)",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750329976033",
          "structured_type": "medication_statement"
        }
      ],
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": "Yes",
          "operator": "equals",
          "question": "Q-1750328670426"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "03c49b6c-25d4-4b28-ad41-10981b8b587f",
      "text": "Why the patient doesn't have any medical reason",
      "type": "string",
      "link_id": "Q-1750330258352",
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": "No",
          "operator": "equals",
          "question": "Q-1750328670426"
        },
        {
          "answer": "Yes",
          "operator": "not_equals",
          "question": "Q-1750328670426"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "cd6249b6-a8d1-4cde-b046-4e8a9fef0b12",
      "text": "Expected date for the medication history to be filled",
      "type": "integer",
      "link_id": "Q-1750333368646",
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": true,
          "operator": "exists",
          "question": "Q-1750330258352"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "7aebc350-eb2a-4c93-bae2-75971a5d7305",
      "text": "what is the profession of the patient",
      "type": "choice",
      "link_id": "Q-1750334310662",
      "answer_option": [
        {
          "value": "Professional"
        },
        {
          "value": "Unskilled labour"
        },
        {
          "value": "Skilled labour"
        },
        {
          "value": "Other"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "a4acfd07-74a5-4c71-af9f-1c28e1859cc8",
      "text": "What is the other profession of the patient",
      "type": "choice",
      "link_id": "Q-1750334914724",
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": "Other",
          "operator": "equals",
          "question": "Q-1750334310662"
        }
      ],
      "answer_option": [
        {
          "value": "Business Men"
        },
        {
          "value": "Entrepreneur"
        },
        {
          "value": "Home Maker"
        },
        {
          "value": "Retired Person"
        },
        {
          "value": "N/A"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "5ba4226e-1c54-4244-ac5b-ae255f3da4fe",
      "text": "Provide Links to patient reports, if any",
      "type": "url",
      "link_id": "Q-1750333852096"
    },
    {
      "id": "87c4da64-52e4-484e-b6aa-84593d3cdf0e",
      "text": "Patient shared which all information to calculate BMI",
      "type": "choice",
      "link_id": "Q-1750335431719",
      "repeats": true,
      "answer_option": [
        {
          "value": "Height"
        },
        {
          "value": "Weight"
        },
        {
          "value": "N/A"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "f2639091-128d-400d-a6ac-f6168961bdf6",
      "text": "Preferred next consultation date ",
      "type": "date",
      "link_id": "Q-1750334093849",
      "required": true
    },
    {
      "id": "f23bbd91-4835-422d-9d65-55e5d19a9645",
      "text": "Preferred next consultation time",
      "type": "time",
      "link_id": "Q-1750333933325",
      "required": true
    },
    {
      "id": "cbdc3187-d1b7-4bfb-8ca5-edd4f928e90c",
      "text": "Remarks if any",
      "type": "text",
      "link_id": "Q-1750335593759"
    },
    {
      "id": "6e7f8bfd-389b-4852-9990-c2c5061e12af",
      "text": "How did the patient rate the services",
      "type": "integer",
      "link_id": "Q-1750335635057"
    },
    {
      "id": "ba2ad77a-5165-4a01-94ec-2dd3953e5c8d",
      "text": "Why its rated less or equal to 8",
      "type": "text",
      "link_id": "Q-1750335681228",
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": 0,
          "operator": "less_or_equals",
          "question": "Q-1750335635057"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "1016de1b-3472-418f-8726-dda4d2ac704e",
      "text": "Why its rated greater than 8",
      "type": "text",
      "link_id": "Q-1750335770581",
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": 8,
          "operator": "greater",
          "question": "Q-1750335635057"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "23dc46b6-66e6-4971-8fef-e91c020245de",
      "text": "Display",
      "type": "display",
      "link_id": "Q-1750333628672",
      "description": "Note: All information is confidential"
    },
    {
      "id": "4a471d97-4928-4261-9362-98dde0d2a8f3",
      "text": "Below are the clinical record of the patient",
      "type": "text",
      "link_id": "Q-1750336197774",
      "read_only": true
    },
    {
      "id": "f473430a-3f91-41c3-a3aa-5f712c8614ea",
      "text": "Structured question of the clinical Record",
      "type": "group",
      "link_id": "Q-1750337803684",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": "22334d2b-db40-4b04-9fdb-4e4d0d4a7d3b",
          "text": "Allergies",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750337836896",
          "structured_type": "allergy_intolerance"
        },
        {
          "id": "311b0631-5d29-4e9a-97b8-3ccf740f6cbc",
          "text": "Symptom",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750338077262",
          "structured_type": "symptom"
        },
        {
          "id": "82ab8c0b-f6cd-42ce-9f0a-3348dc1ff042",
          "text": "Diagnosis",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750338100618",
          "structured_type": "diagnosis"
        },
        {
          "id": "6082f402-573a-4ead-8e30-1e5cec563463",
          "text": "Encounter",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750338117891",
          "structured_type": "encounter"
        },
        {
          "id": "8fb09a25-faa7-4c1c-a9c8-96c8ee3a0843",
          "text": "Time of death",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750338131186",
          "structured_type": "time_of_death"
        },
        {
          "id": "347774ed-036b-417b-b37f-7984d86a7c0f",
          "text": "Appointment",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750338152209",
          "structured_type": "appointment"
        },
        {
          "id": "7c4a7eaa-0313-45f6-8aa1-2f721210ed05",
          "text": "Files",
          "type": "structured",
          "link_id": "Q-1750338173626",
          "structured_type": "files"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "e622ec12-ee9f-4427-9d6f-f931bf38edc9",
      "text": "what is the patients temperature (Normal 37 degree C)",
      "type": "decimal",
      "unit": {
        "code": "Cel",
        "system": "http://unitsofmeasure.org",
        "display": "degree Celsius"
      },
      "link_id": "Q-1750338220704"
    },
    {
      "id": "0b38fa2c-8669-4501-bc56-6e81b5441836",
      "text": "Reason for lower temperature (  <37 )",
      "type": "text",
      "link_id": "Q-1750338359523",
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": 37,
          "operator": "less",
          "question": "Q-1750338220704"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "c2ffbd75-2ffa-4b39-a26a-ca1c36aa703b",
      "text": "Reason for higher temperature (38)",
      "type": "string",
      "link_id": "Q-1750338361995",
      "enable_when": [
        {
          "answer": 38,
          "operator": "greater_or_equals",
          "question": "Q-1750338220704"
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "status": "draft",
  "subject_type": "encounter",
  "version": "",
  "tags": []
}